<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-12-29T20:13:54-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">The Young &amp;amp; Stupid Show</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Kodak’s Failure</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2018/12/29/december-test.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Kodak's Failure" /><published>2018-12-29T07:06:41-06:00</published><updated>2018-12-29T07:06:41-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2018/12/29/december-test</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2018/12/29/december-test.html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;kodaks-failure&quot;&gt;Kodak’s Failure&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you grew up in the era of “the Kodak moment,” the eventual downfall of the consumer film giant would be hard to foresee, especially when considering the fact that the first digital camera was invented by Kodak’s own engineers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1976, Kodak sat on top of the amateur photography hill with a firm hold on the market. They made 90% of film sales and 85% of camera sales in the US. They brought photography out from the chemical baths of darkrooms and put it snugly into our pockets with the invention of the snapshot camera. Taking and sharing photos has been a staple of modern culture ever since, and Kodak arguably played the largest part in the personal photography phenomenon of the 20th century.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, where did everything go wrong?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like most of the companies that perished in the aftermath of the digital revolution, they made the costly mistake of trying to move forward by standing still.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Steve Sasson, the Kodak engineer responsible for inventing the world’s first digital camera, presented his creation to the seniors at Kodak in 1975, he was shrugged off. The invention was impressive, but it negated the use of film, which is how Kodak made most of their revenue at the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They ran a “razor and blades” operation, offering cameras as inexpensively as possible, and exceeding margins by selling consumables like film, chemicals, and paper. A camera that didn’t need film, chemicals, or paper was clearly a landmark invention for the industry, but it didn’t fit into Kodak’s business plan, and was thusly ignored.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the time digital cameras became more affordable, making their way into the mainstream market during the turn of the millennium, Kodak was already years behind companies like Sony and Canon. They found moderate success during the mid 2000’s by making low end DSLRs for consumers and continued to dominate in the film sector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The film sector, however, which had at one point been the company’s greatest strength, began to shrink at a rapid pace as the 2010’s approached. This, along with the increased competition in the digital camera market, proved to be too much. In 2012, after 120+ years of business, Kodak filed for bankruptcy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aside from refusing to adopt digital cameras early on, the most significant missed opportunity for Kodak was the acquisition of Ofoto. Ofoto, later renamed Kodak Gallery, was an online service that began in 1999. It allowed users to upload, share, print, and view photos they and their friends had taken. Sound familiar?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kodak was the first to the snapshot camera, the digital camera, and an Instagram predecessor. It wasn’t that they didn’t realize the significance of each of these inventions, but that they were worried it would have a negative impact on the success they had found through selling film.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ironically, they were right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;sources&quot;&gt;Sources&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;https://valuer.ai/blog/50-examples-of-corporations-that-failed-to-innovate-and-missed-their-chance/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;https://www.collectivecampus.com.au/blog/10-companies-that-were-too-slow-to-respond-to-change&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;https://www.forbes.com/sites/chunkamui/2012/01/18/how-kodak-failed/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;https://www.quora.com/Why-did-Kodak-fail-despite-having-invented-the-digital-camera&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;https://blogs.wsj.com/source/2012/02/26/the-demise-of-kodak-five-reasons/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kodak&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Kodak’s Failure</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Welcome to Jekyll!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2018/11/21/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to Jekyll!" /><published>2018-11-21T07:06:41-06:00</published><updated>2018-11-21T07:06:41-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2018/11/21/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2018/11/21/welcome-to-jekyll.html">&lt;p&gt;You’ll find this post in your &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add new posts, simply add a file in the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory that follows the convention &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YYYY-MM-DD-name-of-post.ext&lt;/code&gt; and includes the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;'Tom'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints 'Hi, Tom' to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/docs/home&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;. If you have questions, you can ask them on &lt;a href=&quot;https://talk.jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll Talk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">You’ll find this post in your _posts directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run jekyll serve, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.</summary></entry></feed>